Hello.
こんにちは
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いですね
It feels fresh.
フレッシュな感じで
He's such a famous person, right?
すごい有名人なんでしょ?
I have a lot of followers on Instagram.
ちょっとインスタのフォロワー多いくらいです
Is it a bit much?
ちょっと多い?
It's a bit much.
ちょっと多い
How many people?
何人くらいですか?
There are about 250,000 people now.
今25万人くらい
That's too many.
多すぎるね
It's not just a little bit.
ちょっとじゃないじゃん
Someone famous?
有名な方?
I don't think it's too much though.
あんまりだと思いますけど
I think she is quite famous among the models.
モデルの中では結構有名な方だと思います
Is that so?
そうなの?
Are you a model?
モデルさんをやってる?
that's right.
そうです
I see.
なるほどね
It's an acceptable style.
納得のスタイルだね
What kind of activities do you usually do?
普段どういう活動をしたりしてるの?
I usually appear in a lot of magazines.
普段雑誌とか結構出てます
TV, etc.
テレビとかも
tv set?
テレビ?
TV or something.
テレビとか
That's right.
そうなんだ
You're such a celebrity.
めちゃくちゃ芸能人してるね
Is your job difficult?
大変ですか仕事?
But it's fun.
でも楽しいですよ
Although it can be difficult sometimes.
大変なこともありますけど
fun?
楽しい?
That's right.
そうなんだ
Was that always your dream?
もともとそうなるの夢だったの?
I agree.
そうですね
It's been like that on TV for a long time.
昔からテレビでそういうの
I'm out.
出 ました
That's right.
そうなんだ
Is there a celebrity you admire?
憧れの芸能人さんとかいる?
I'm here.
います
there is.
あります
There are a few people though.
何人かですけど
For example, who?
例えば誰ですか?
for example...
例えば...
Just a moment here...
ちょっとここで...
I can't say that.
言えないよね
That's right.
そうなんだ
So, are you used to being photographed like this?
じゃあこう撮られたりするのは 慣れてるかな?
I'm suddenly turning it around though.
急に回しちゃってるけど
I'm quite used to being photographed.
撮られること自体は結構慣れてます
That's right.
そうだよね
That's the kind of job it is.
そういうお仕事だもんね
You're answering clearly and clearly.
ちゃんとね、ハキハキ 答えてくれてるけど
All of a sudden, are you that naughty?
いきなりね そんなヘッチなの?
There's no such thing as a hectic one, right?
ヘッチなのないでしょ?
No.
ないです
It's my first time.
初めてです
I just caught a glimpse of her body, and her style is really nice.
さっき体チラッと見ちゃったけど すごいスタイルいいよね
thank you.
ありがとう
What about Gravia?
グラウィアとかは?
Are you wearing a swimsuit?
水着とか着て?
It's not there anymore.
もうないですね
That's right...
そう いう...
H series...
H系の...
There's no H type...
H系の...ないんだ
yes.
はい
I see.
そっか
Today, I thought I'd take a little photo of your body.
今日はちょっとね 体をね、ちょっと撮らせてもらおうかなって
Yeah, yeah, that's the feeling.
そうそう そう、感じだよ
Are you interested in that?
そういうのが興味はある?
Things that are naughty.
ヘッチなことは
I'm a little interested.
ちょっと興味あります
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏とかいます?
No, it's not there.
いや、いないです
not present?
いない?
I'm having more fun at work now.
今お仕事の方が楽しいので
I see.
そっか
Work, I'm busy.
仕事ね、忙しいからね
Stay focused.
集中してね
I'm sure it'll be popular though.
モテるだろうけど
How many people have experience?
経験人数とかは?
By the way.
ちなみに
There are only about 2 people.
2人くらいしかないです
Isn't that so?
それはそうでしょ
Normally.
普通に
2 people?
2人?
TRUE?
本当?
They are two well-chosen people.
ちゃんと選んだ2人なんだ
Likely to be chosen.
選ばれしい
What do you like?
何が好きですか?
Her legs look long too.
足も長そう
People often say it's long.
よく長いって言われます
Because it's a model.
モデルなので
That's right.
そうだよね
It's amazing when you actually see it
実際見ると、すごい
Not only is it thin, but it also has a slight glimmer to it.
細 いだけじゃなくて ちょっと チラチラ チラチラ見える
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Just a glimpse.
チラチラ見えるだけ
That's amazing.
すごいよね
This one too.
こっちの方も
I'm nervous.
緊張してるんで
緊張してます
Why is it my first time?
初めてなんで
That's right.
そうだよね
A little long legs.
ちょっと長い足を
I don't often cut off models' legs.
モデルさんの足切るの あんまないんで
I think I'll change the smell a bit.
ちょっと 匂い変えとこうかなと
It's a raspberry scent.
ラズベリーの香りだね
I don't do that much.
そんなにしません
What is it?
なんだろう?
a little bit.
ちょっと
That's it.
そんな
Are you going to do that?
そんなことしてやるの?
I just stabbed you.
今俺が刺したんだけど
Have you ever been teased with your feet?
足でいじめたことある?
No.
ないです
Is that how you feel?
そんな感じですか?
That's what it feels like.
そんな感じ
This is better.
こっちの方がいい
amazing.
すごい
Do you understand that?
そういうの分かるの?
I wondered if there was anything I could do with my feet.
足でできることなんかないかなって
I'll stand up for a moment.
ちょっと 立つから
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
You're a little nervous, aren't you?
ちょっと緊張してるでしょ
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
It's long.
長いね
Is it long?
長いですか?
Under the model.
モデルさんの下
Wow, right away.
すごい、すぐ
I'll touch it right away.
すぐ触っちゃうのそんな
Because it's from above.
上からだから
Is it OK from above?
上からはOK?
Don't you like it?
好きなんじゃない?
a little bit.
ちょっと
What is naughty?
エッチなことは?
It's normal.
普通です
It's a super cute outfit though.
超かわいい服なんだけど
this is?
これは?
Bring it back.
戻して
Huh?
あれ?
Take this for a moment.
ちょっとこれを
If you turn it over.
めくっちゃうと
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
amazing.
すごい
amazing
Something.
なんか
It's getting a little damp, though.
ちょっと 湿ってきてるけど、これ
Slimy.
ぬめぬめ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
This is so slimy.
すごいぬめぬめしてる、これ
That's amazing, hey.
すごいよ、ちょっと
Hold both legs.
両足をさ、 抱える
Hold it in your hand.
手で持ってさ
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
this.
これ
It's completely visible.
丸見えだよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
That's amazing, seriously.
すごいね、まじで
It's a bit yellow, isn't it?
イエロいね、ちょっと
It's a mess.
め ちゃくちゃ
Try standing up, try standing up.
立ってみて立ってみて
Because I can't see it at all.
全然ちょっと見えないから
It's a little hot, isn't it?
ちょっと熱いでしょ?
It's a little hot.
ちょっと熱いです
It's hot.
熱いね
Well then, let's take our clothes off.
じゃあ 脱 いでいこうか
amazing.
すごい
The cleavage.
谷間が
Were you dressed like that?
そんな格好してたの?
A
イ エ ロ
You look good.
い 格好してるね
I like the style.
すげースタイルいいね
Well, that's true.
まあ、そりゃそうなんだけどね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'll keep looking at this.
ずっと眺めちゃうね、これね
Turn around and give me a little push.
ちょっと押しに後ろ向いてね
I've got a little hands on it.
ちょっと手ついてさ
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
amazing.
すごい
Please turn around for a moment.
ちょっとこっち振り向いてみて
Yellow.
イエロい
You're looking great.
すげー格好してるじゃん
The crack.
割れ目が
The crack is transparent though.
割れ目がスケスケだけど
No lewd undercoat.
スケベの下毛がない
is that so?
そうですか?
The crack is transparent though.
割れ目がスケスケだけど
Did you know?
知ってたの?
I didn't know.
知らなかった
I didn't know, did you know?
知らないで、知ってたの?
That's stupid.
そんなバカな
It's really messy.
すげーぐしゃぐしゃになってるよ
It's super wet.
超濡れてる
What is this undercoat?
なにこの下毛
Don't you know?
知ってないの?
It's a mess though.
ぐしゃぐしゃになってるけどね
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Sit down again.
もう一度座って
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
Delicious breasts.
おいしいおっぱい
It's soft.
柔らかいね
Are you excited to be photographed?
撮られて興奮してるの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I can't help but make such naughty sounds.
こんなエッチな音しちゃおうないもんね
good?
いい?
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
It came out.
出てきちゃったね
Sorry, that's amazing.
ごめん、すごい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's a mess.
めちゃくちゃじゃん
Great style.
すーげースタイル
It's mine, with both hands.
自分のさ、両手でさ
Pull up your pussy.
おまんこ引き上げてごらん
Show me here.
ここ見せて
delicious.
おいしい
Chinchi
ちんち
Hmm, you like it, right?
ん 好きでしょ?
I like it.
好きです
I don't have the voice to say it clearly
なかなかはっきり言う声いないけど
hey.
ね
Don't you want to take a look at it?
ち んちんちょっと見たいんじゃない?
You want to see it, right?
見たいでしょ?
Ah, good at it.
あ、上手
That's amazing.
すごいね
You're good at it.
上手だね
While touching my dick.
ちんちん触りながらさ
Very good at it.
すごい上手
That's amazing.
すごいね
Hey, you want to try it, right?
ちょっとさ、やってみたいでしょ?
Just a little.
ちょっとさ
This is what it looks like.
ほっぱいでこうさ
Try sandwiching this.
挟 んでみてこれ
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
across
挟んで
difference.
さ
On the cheeks and on both sides.
ほ っぱいで、両サイドで
You've never done it before, have you?
挟 むの、やったことないでしょ?
No.
ないです
Pinch it tightly.
きゅーっと挟んで
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
It's my first experience.
初体験だね
First experience.
初体験
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだよ
It's better to do it this way.
こうやってやったほうがいいよ
That's amazing.
すごいね
Are you having sex?
エッチをしてるの?
Haven't you?
してないの?
I haven't.
してないです
Haven't you?
してないの?
for a while.
しばらく
It’s been a while?
しばらくぶり?
It's been a while.
しばらくぶりです
Do you want to have sex?
エッチするの?
A little bit of rum.
ラムはちょっと
picture?
え?
I want you to wear rubber.
ゴムはつけてほしいです
Eh, rubber?
え、ゴム?
why?
なんで?
What have you never done?
なんまでしたことないの?
I've never done it.
したことない
It's okay, but it feels good.
大丈夫だけど、気持ちいいよな
There are also game activities.
ゲームの活動とかあるし
It's a bit of a problem if you make a joke.
ニジンしたらちょっといけないの
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
I don't say anything.
ニジンしないって
But there are activities.
でも、活動とかあるから
You want to have sex, right?
エッチしたいでしょ、でも
I need you to do the rubber.
ゴムやってくれないと
Are you scared?
怖いの?
Yeah.
うん
Just a little bit is fine.
ちょっとだけいいじゃん
No.
ダメです
No?
ダメ?
Seriously?
まじで?
lie?
嘘?
Well then, let's put some on.
じゃあ、ちょっとつけようか
It's scary.
怖いもんね
Is there any?
あるかな?
I don't usually carry it around.
普段持ち歩いてないんだよね
Because I don't wear it.
つけないからさ
Turn it on, you suck.
つけろ、最低な
There it was, there it was.
あった、あった
The nails.
爪が
Don't get it all the way to the roots.
根元までつけない
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Nails.
爪がね
Because my nails are a little long.
爪がちょっと長いから
You know exactly how to put it on.
つけ方ちゃんと分かるんだね
That's great.
偉いね
Always wear it properly.
ちゃんとつけるんだ、いつも
I always wear it.
いつもつけてます
An ex-boyfriend or something.
元彼とか
That's great.
偉いね
Now that's it, right?
これで、これでいいでしょ
Can I hold you here?
ここ抱えてもいい?
Something like this.
こういうの
It stings.
チクにさ
Ask me to lick you
舐めてもらって
good?
いい?
Chinky, touch me.
チ ンキー、触って
Awesome.
すげー
Can I eat your hands and feet?
手足食べてもいい?
Are you slowly moving it in and out?
ゆっくり出し入れしてるの?
It's going to be crazy.
めっちゃくるってさ
Chinky
チンキーを
I put it on my waist.
腰 ペタってつけた
I put it on my shoulders.
肩ペタってつけた
This feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ、これ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Right?
で しょ
Hey.
ねえ
I wonder why this feels so good.
なんで気持ちいいんだろうね、これ
Manjul is overflowing.
マンジュルが 結構溢れちゃってるね
Manjul is a little Manjul is Manjul,
マンジュルが ちょっとマンジュルが マンジュルだからね、
this.
これ
I agree.
そうだね
Just take it off.
ほんま外してさ
Can I put it on my breasts?
おっぱいにかけていい?
Just take it off and put it on your breasts.
ほんま外して、おっぱいにかけるよ
Manjul.
マンジュルが
Hey, wake up your upper body.
ちょっとさ、上半身起こして
Even if I pick it up.
出し拾っても
On your breasts.
おっぱいにね
I put it on.
かけちゃった